Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series V. BY-LAWS
  - Sub-Series 204-936. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 936-Galv. Con. Off. Lodge, Galveston, Texas / Lodge No. 936, H.V. Freight Handlers Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1921-1947 (Box 23, Folder 58)
      Nov. 8, 1947; 1921-24.
  - Sub-Series 204-942. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 942-Wolverine Lodge, Jackson, Michigan, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 59)
      Feb. 29, 1953.
  - Sub-Series 204-943. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 943-Washington Lodge, Jonesboro, Georgia, 1933-1959 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 204-944. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 944-Power City Lodge, Niagara Falls, Ontario, Canada, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 204-946. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 946-Coronation Lodge, Argentia, Newfoundland, Canada, 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 204-948. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 948-Bonsecours Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1921-1958 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 204-949. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 949-Scranton Lodge, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1938-1957 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 204-953. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 953-Swift Current Lodge, Swift Current, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1940-1950 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 204-954. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 954-Cedar Rapids Lodge, Cedar Rapids, Iowa, 1928-1949 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-956. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 956-McAdoo Lodge, Decatur, Georgia, 1935-1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-958. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 958-Brookhatten Lodge, New York City, New York, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-961. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 961-Harlan County Lodge, Harlan, Kentucky, 1938-1959 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 204-971. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 971-Fort Schuyler Lodge, Utica, New York, 1941-1951 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-972. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 972-Progressive Lodge, Rochester, New York, 1937-1959 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-973. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 973-Union Pacific Lodge, Denver, Colorado, 1945-1956 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 204-977. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 977-Old Dominion Lodge, Richmond, Virginia, 1940-1950 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-979. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 979-Rock River Lodge, Rockford, Illinois, 1922 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-983. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 983-Fortieth Anniversary Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 204-985. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 985-King George Lodge, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1921-1954 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-986. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 986-Hudson Harbor Lodge, Graham Beach, Staten Island, New York, 1941-1956 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-987. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 987-Pacific Fruit Express Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1938-1951 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 204-990. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 990-Eastern Terminal Lodge, Queens Village, New York, 1944-1946 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 204-991. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 991-Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railroad Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1936-1959 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-992. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 992-Progress Lodge, Waltham, Massachusetts, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-993. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 993-Central Lodge, Elizabeth, New Jersey, 1948-1959 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-996. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 996-Transcontinental Lodge, Seattle, Washington, 1939-1959 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-1004. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1004-Debardeurs Cotiers Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1940-1951 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-1014. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1014-Tamiens(?) Lodge, Jacksonville, Florida, 1941-1959 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-1017. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1017-Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Lodge, 1937-1959 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 204-1019. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1019-Boise Lodge, Nampa, Idaho, 1950-1959 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-1020. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1020-Gawps Lodge, College Park, Georgia, 1941-1948 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-1021. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1021-Brisley Lodge, Battle Creek, Michigan, 1944-1959 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-1024. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1024-Big Four Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1943-1955 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-1026. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1026-Pioneer Northwest Lodge, Spokane, Washington, 1924-1959 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 204-1027. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1027-Old Reliable Lodge, Augusta, Georgia, 1942-1950 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-1033. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1033-Middletown Lodge, Middletown, New York, 1944-1953 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-1037. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1037-Fayette Lodge, Lexington, Kentucky, 1936-1959 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-1039. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1039-Bay Cities Lodge, El Cerrito, California, 1920-1959 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-1043. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1043-Grand Central Lodge, Ozone Park, New York, 1927-1959 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 204-1045. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1045-Peake Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1942-1959 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-1046. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1046-Calhoun Lodge, North Charleston, South Carolina, 1938-1959 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-1047. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1047-Jackson Lodge, Berwin, Illinois, 1953-1959 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-1054. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1054-Tamaleais Lodge, Petaluma, California, 1931-1955 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-1055. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1055-Fruit Growers Express Lodge, Belleville, New Jersey, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-1059. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1059-L. S. Richmond Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1921-1959 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 204-1069. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1069-Communipaw Lodge, Kenilworth, New Jersey, 1948-1955 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 204-1071. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1071-Poinciani Acme Lodge, West Palm Beach, Florida, 1952-1959 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 204-1073. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1073-Electric City Lodge, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1948-1959 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 204-1074. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1074-Independence Lodge, Norwalk, Iowa, 1926-1959 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 204-1078. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1078-Tri Building Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1943-1956 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 204-1081. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1081-Rocco Lodge, Mobile, Alabama, 1933-1959 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 204-1082. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1082-John H. Benton Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 204-1083. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1083-Southern Lodge, Covington, Kentucky, 1922-1945 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 204-1084. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1084-Progressive Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1920-1951 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 204-1085. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1085-Prairie City Lodge, Fargo, North Dakota, 1937-1959 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 204-1086. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1086-Place Viger Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1925-1951 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 204-1089. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1089-Boston Terminal Company Lodge, Jamaica Plain, Massachusetts, 1947-1957 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 204-1090. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1090-McArthur Lodge, Roanoke, Virginia, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 204-1092. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1092-Victory Lodge, East Dubuque, Illinois, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 204-1094. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1094-Dining Car Lodge, Ridgewood, New York, 1944-1959 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 204-1095. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1095-Victory Lodge, St. Albans, Vermont, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 204-1096. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1096-Somerville Lodge, Somerville, Texas, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 56)
      Nov. 4, 1944.
  - Sub-Series 204-1097. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1097-Progressive Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1925-1929 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 204-1107. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1107-Liberal Lodge, Liberal, Kansas, 1922-1959 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 204-1114. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1114-Casper Lodge, Casper, Wyoming, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 204-1127. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1127-Art Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 204-1135. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1135-Rio Grande Lodge, El Paso, Texas, 1945-1959 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 204-1150. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1150-W.E. Williams Lodge, Kansas City, Kansas, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 204-1154. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1154-Sumter Lodge, Sumter, South Carolina, 1934-1937 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 204-1161. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1161-Ottawa Lodge, Hull, Quebec, Canada, 1927-1959 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 204-1171. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1171-Kansas City Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1946-1959 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 204-1173. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1173-Trailway Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1950-1959 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 204-1176. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1176-WW + IB(?) Lodge, Omaha, Nebraska, 1920-1959 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 204-1177. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1177-Roosevelt Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1927-1954 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 204-1183. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1183-Pershing Square Lodge, New York City, New York, 1953-1959 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 204-1185. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1185-Puget Sound Lodge, Tacoma, Washington, 1933-1959 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 204-1186. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1186-Yard Clerks Lodge, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 204-1188. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1188-Victory Lodge, Argentia, Newfoundland, Canada, 1947-1959 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 204-1189. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1189-Lakeshore Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1929-1960 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 204-1191. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1191-Point St. Charles Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1920-1921 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 204-1192. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1192-Central General Office Lodge, Wyandotte, Michigan, 1927-1959 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 204-1198. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1198-Wood Street Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1927-1949 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 204-1199. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1199-East Cambridge Lodge, Somerville, Massachusetts, 1944-1953 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 204-1200. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1200-Friendship Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1948-1951 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 204-1202. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1202-New Smyrna Lodge, New Smyrna Beach, Florida, 1938-1959 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 204-1203. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1203-Midland Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1947-1956 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 204-1205. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1205-Murray Hill Lodge, New York, New York, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-1209. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1209-Gulf Division Lodge, Laurel, Mississippi, 1927-1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-1211. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1211-Phoenician Lodge, Phoenix, Arizona, 1949-1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-1218. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1218-Clarence Mullen Lodge, Narbeth, Pennsylvania, 1951-1953 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 204-1220. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1220-Tampa, Florida, 1941-1942 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-1225. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1225-Chadron Lodge, Chadron, Nebraska, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-1227. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1227-Mission Overland Lodge, San Gabriel, California, 1921-1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 204-1229. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1229-Allen Lodge, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1921-1953 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-1223. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1223-Victory Lodge, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1933-1959 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-1236. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1236-Renovo Lodge, Renovo, Pennsylvania, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 204-1248. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1248-Buffalo General Office Lodge, West Seneca, New York, 1940-1959 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-1249. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1249-Leewood Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-1250. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1250-Hornets Nest Lodge, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1927-1959 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 204-1254. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1254-Kansas City Terminal Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1923-1957 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 204-1262. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1262-Especo Lodge, Portland, Oregon, 1928-1959 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-1269. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1269-Prairie Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1936-1954 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-1270. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1270-Missouri Pullman Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1951-1959 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-1271. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1271-Florida Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-1272. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1272-Angus Clerks Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-1274. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1274-Proviso Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-1280. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1280-Equity Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 204-1281. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1281-Paris, Tennessee, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-1282. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1282-Pitcairn Stores Lodge, Pitcairn, Pennsylvania, 1953-1957 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-1286. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1286-Boston Freight Handlers Lodge, Somerville, Massachusetts, 1942-1959 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-1289. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1289-Woodgale Lodge, Franklin Park, Illinois, 1951-1957 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-1290. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1290-Laurier Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1930-1959 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 204-1293. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1293-Shelby Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1953-1956 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-1295. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1295-Gate City Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1922-1951 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-1298. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1298-Cleveland Station Employees Lodge, Lyndhurst, Ohio, 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-1299. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1299-Tyler Lodge, Tyler, Texas, 1949-1959 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-1307. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1307-Sherbrooke Lodge, Sherbrooke, Quebec, Canada, 1921-1922 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 204-1310. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1310-Great Northern Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1939-1945 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-1312. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1312-Dixon Lodge, Sterling, Illinois, 1944-1957 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-1315. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1315-Pacific Electric Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1952-1958 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-1333. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1333-Steel Valley Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-1334. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1334-Warwick Lodge, Warwick, New York, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-1338. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1338-Coast Line Lodge, Savannah, Georgia, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 204-1342. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1342-Bayou Lodge, Houston, Texas, 1953-1955 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 204-1343. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1343-Kansas City Southern Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1938-1953 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 204-1353. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1353-Belt Lodge, Houston, Texas, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 204-1356. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1356-New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1955-1958 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 204-1357. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1357-Tejas Lodge, San Antonio, Texas, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 204-1360. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1360-Sunset Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1956-1959 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 204-1362. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1362-Border Cities Lodge, Windsor, Ontario, Canada, 1935-1959 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 204-1370. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1370-Cresson Lodge, Cresson, Pennsylvania, 1920-1921 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 204-1374. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1374-Freight Claim Bureau Lodge, Quinex, Massachusetts, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 204-1375. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1375-Desert View Lodge, Yuma, Arizona, 1956-1959 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 204-1376. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1376-Desert Lodge, Colton, California, 1956-1959 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 204-1377. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1377-Rock Island Lodge, Topeka, Kansas, 1921-1959 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 204-1383. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1383-Stores Department Lodge, Roanoke, Virginia, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 204-1384. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1384-Alyth Lodge, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1929-1930 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 204-1387. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1387-East Coast Lodge, St. Augustine, Florida, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 204-1391. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1391-Choctaw Lodge, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 204-1400. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1400-Tomah Lodge, Tomah, Wisconsin, 1948-1959 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 204-1403. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1403-J.C. Boyer Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1938-1957 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 204-1404. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1404-North Pacific General Office Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 204-1409. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1409-Jones Valley Lodge, Birmingham, Alabama, 1922-1957 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 204-1412. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1412-Ellen Lodge, Overland, Missouri, 1928-1952 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 204-1431. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1431-Arkansas-Louisiana Lodge, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1936-1943 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 204-1435. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1435-Anchorage Lodge, Anchorage, Alaska, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 204-1447. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1447-Santa Fe Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 204-1448. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1448-Worth Lodge, Fort Worth, Texas, 1929-1955 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 204-1461. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1461-Kansas City Southern Lodge, Shreveport, Louisiana, 1939-1959 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 204-1477. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1477-Queen City Lodge, East St. Louis, Illinois, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 204-1478. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1478-Capitol City Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1944-1959 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 204-1489. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1489-Union Pacific Lodge, Kansas City, Kansas, 1934-1953 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 204-1490. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1490-Valley Lodge, Hagerstown, Maryland, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 204-1497. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1497-Vi?o Lodge, Terre Haute, Indiana, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 204-1498. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1498-Diamond City Lodge, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 204-1504. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1504-Great Northern Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 204-1511. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1511-Richmond Lodge, Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 204-1523. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1523-Royal Palm Lodge, Jacksonville, Florida, 1933-1959 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 204-1524. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1524-Belleville Lodge, Belleville, Illinois, 1921-1954 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 204-1525. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1525-McAdam Lodge, McAdam Junction, New Brunswick, Canada, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 204-1526. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1526-Frederiction Lodge, Frederiction, New Brunswick, Canada, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 204-1602. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1602-Benton Lodge, Fort Mitchell, Kentucky, 1934-1949 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 204-1603. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1603-Roosevelt Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1939-1951 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 204-1605. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1605-Wayne Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Sub-Series 204-1608. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1608-Queen City Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 204-1610. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1610-Unity Lodge, Syracuse, New York, 1940-1954 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 204-1611. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1611-Essex Lodge, Newark, New Jersey, 1939-1951 (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 204-1612. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1612-Almonoh Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1938-1950 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 204-1614. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1614-Mayflower Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1945-1957 (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 204-1615. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1615-Forwarding Lodge, Farmingdale, New York, 1942-1959 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 204-1622. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1622-Golden Triangle Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1937-1945 (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 204-1625. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1625-Hub Carloading Lodge, Medford, Massachusetts, 1941-1959 (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 204-1629. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1629-Nutmeg Lodge, New Haven, Connecticut, 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 204-1630. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1630-International Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Sub-Series 204-1633. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1633-Great Lakes Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 204-1634. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1634-Buffalo Acme Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1934-1958 (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Sub-Series 204-1635. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1635-Acme Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Sub-Series 204-1639. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1639-Affco Lodge, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Sub-Series 204-1640. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1640-Acme Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1939-1958 (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Sub-Series 204-1644. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 1644-Lincoln Lodge, Brooklyn, New York, 1940-1957 (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - Sub-Series 204-2004. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2004-Angelus Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1930-1959 (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Sub-Series 204-2005. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2005-Maryland Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1948-1952 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 204-2007. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2007-Fort Sutter Lodge, Sacramento, California, 1932-1933 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 204-2009. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2009-Queen City Lodge, Denver, Colorado, 1924-1959 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-2010. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2010-Railway Expressmen's Lodge, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1929-1959 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-2013. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2013-Capitol City Lodge, Denison, Kansas, 1923-1959 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-2014. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2014-Missing Link Lodge, Colorado Springs, Colorado, 1924-1951 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 204-2016. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2016-Omaha Expressmen Lodge, Omaha, Nebraska, 1921-1951 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-2017. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2017-Eminence Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1920-1959 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-2024. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2024-Gateway Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1920-1968 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 204-2025. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2025-Railway Express Messengers Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1922-1936 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-2028. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2028-North and South Lodge, Wollaston, Massachusetts, 1949-1959 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-2029. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 2029-Itasca Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1922-1959 (Box 26, Folder 12)